<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ben Rasich</title>
    <link>https://brasich.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ben Rasich</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://brasich.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://brasich.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 17:13:29 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://brasich.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Crit Season 2022</title>
      <link>https://brasich.github.io/posts/road-season-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 17:13:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brasich.github.io/posts/road-season-2022/</guid>
      <description>The past 6 months have been, without question, the wildest of my adult life. All of it was a lot - packing up my stuff and moving to Denver, school ramping up, work getting crazy - but the one thing that I&amp;rsquo;m sure will always make me giddy as I look back at this period was the ridiculous stuff I got to be a part of on the bike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online Data Science Masters - 1st Semester Review</title>
      <link>https://brasich.github.io/posts/online-data-science-masters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 17:24:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brasich.github.io/posts/online-data-science-masters/</guid>
      <description>After 3 years on the job I&amp;rsquo;m studying for a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Data Science at UT Austin. Is it going to be worth it? Will it be manageable alongside work and other hobbies? Your guess is as good as mine.
How did I get here? The first 3 years of my career leading to my current role as a senior data scientist have been self-taught. I took a job as a business analyst in pursuit of a faster-paced work environment and the greater ownership of complete products that a more digital-focused role allowed over the mechanical engineering field I went to school for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Rise and Fall of Rebake</title>
      <link>https://brasich.github.io/posts/the-rise-and-fall-of-rebake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 15:19:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brasich.github.io/posts/the-rise-and-fall-of-rebake/</guid>
      <description>I was in middle school when Apple opened the App Store. Having mowed lawns for a summer to save up for an iPod Touch, I thought the next logical step was to make an app myself. I had no idea how to begin, no problem I was looking to solve, and after a few hours fumbling around in xcode, trying to understand what the documentation meant by &amp;lsquo;function argument&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;API&amp;rsquo;, that project quickly fizzled out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby&#39;s First Azure Function</title>
      <link>https://brasich.github.io/posts/babys-first-azure-function/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 20:38:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brasich.github.io/posts/babys-first-azure-function/</guid>
      <description>Our team practices a fairly standard separation of responsibilities between Data Science and Engineering. On the data science side, I take in requirements from the business, frame those requirements into a tractable problem, and build a model using all available data. Outside of the model build itself, though, I rely on close partnership with engineers to make data available for me in the production environment and serve up predictions to clients through some sort of production infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Internet Pumpkin Pie Showdown</title>
      <link>https://brasich.github.io/posts/pumpkin-pie-showdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 20:28:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brasich.github.io/posts/pumpkin-pie-showdown/</guid>
      <description>Fall: the leaves are changing, it&amp;rsquo;s too cold for shorts but not cold enough for skiing, and the sun seemingly sets before it rises. It&amp;rsquo;s easily near the bottom of my personal list of the top 4 best seasons on earth.
What fall does have, though, is a near-perfect lineup of seasonal baked goods. From apple crumb cakes to snickerdoodles, the coalescence of the harvest and weather-induced boredom has given rise to an incredible pantheon of autumnal delicacies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>https://brasich.github.io/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 10:41:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brasich.github.io/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Testing out the workflow for blogging with Hugo. It&amp;rsquo;s a goal of mine to start writing more and documenting my projects. It&amp;rsquo;s been a real pain trying to find a way to cheaply host a site on my own domain that gives me enough customization to be fun. It seems like this combination of Hugo + Github Pages will be useful, but I&amp;rsquo;ll have to give it some time.
Currently the process is set up as follows:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
